I can't believe they actually
arrested you as a spy.
Heaven is truly helping me.
As long as I kill you to silence you,
no one will know my identity.
Y-Y-You stay away.
But that power in you is very special.
It'd be a pity to just kill you.
Why don't I dig out
your spiritual veins first?
Stay away from me!
Don't worry. The Demonic Sect's
soul-extracting curse is very fast.
Once you become an empty shell,
no one will know my identity.
U-U-Uncle...
Sect Leader, her old injuries
haven't healed,
and she has new ones.
Plus the shock,
she needs to take some medicine
and rest well.
Hmm, I got it.
Then I will take my leave first.
What does the doctor mean
by leaving the medicine here?
Does he expect me
to feed that girl myself?
Why are mortals so troublesome?
Sect Leader.
It's nothing. Please continue,
Come back.
What is it? Speak.
The spy you caught last night
using Ms. Kong as bait
had a Demonic Sect mark on his arm.
But he has already taken poison
and killed himself.
I know.
You stay and take care of her.
The Sect Leader really cares
about Ms. Kong.
Looks like it's necessary to have
everyone change how they address her.
It's so dark.
Come with me.
Who? Who is talking?
You said you would stay with me
lifetime after lifetime.
No!
This voice again.
What is it calling?
Sister, what's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
I'm fine.
Just had a messy dream.
Someone was talking to me in the dream,
but I can't remember anything.
Don't be afraid, Sister.
Dreams are fake.
When I was little, I often dreamed of being
chased and beaten by the old monster.
I was fine when I woke up.
Aren't you still often chased
and beaten by him now?
Sister, let me tell you a secret.
Although the old monster keeps
a straight face every day,
he is actually very afraid
of being lonely.
He has lived for over a thousand years.
The people around him either died or left.
Don't mind him being fierce to you now.
He actually... probably just doesn't know
how to treat someone well.
Afraid of being lonely?
Lived for over a thousand years?
So, Sister,
don't be afraid of him.
If you can make him smile more,
maybe he won't bear to let you go.
What do you take me for? A pistachio?
Yeah.
A thousand-year-old monster
afraid of loneliness,
and me who remembers nothing.
In a way,
we don't seem to be any different.